The Guide to the American Short Line Railroad Association records, 1912-1971
American Short Line Railroad Association records, 1912-1971
- Series I. Association Records, 1923, 191965.
  - "1954 Annual Meeting, New York"; Oct. 19/20, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    Annotated transcript
  - "1954 Annual Meeting, New York: Annual 1954 - Agenda"; Aug. 2, 1954 to Sept. 28, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Lists, correspondence
  - "Annual, 10-10-55, Chicago: Annual Meeting, 1955"; Feb. 7, 1955 to Dec. 6, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - "Annual, 10-10-55, Chicago: Proceedings"; Oct. 11/12, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Proceedings
  - "Annual, 10-10-55, Chicago: Proceedings"; May 20, 1955 to Dec. 21, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - "Annual, 10-10-55, Chicago: Annual 1955 - Agenda"; July 25, 1955 to Oct. 15, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Pamphlet, correspondence, lists
  - "Annual, 9-24-56, Denver"; Oct. 13, 1955 to May 13, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    Correspondence, lists, itinerary
  - "Annual, 9-24-56, Denver: Annual Meeting Agenda"; June 17, 1956 to Aug. 10, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Lists, correspondence, report
  - "Annual, 9-24-56, Denver: Annual 1956 - Proceedings"; Oct. 11, 1956 to Dec. 5, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - "Annual, 9-30-57, New Orleans: 1957 Annual Meeting"; Apr. 21, 1956 to Nov. 21, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    Correspondence, lists, clippings, tourist guides
  - "Annual, 9-30-57, New Orleans: 1957 Annual Meeting"; September, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - "Annual, 9-30-57, New Orleans" Pullman Refund, 1957"; Oct. 4, 1957 to Dec. 6, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - "Annual, 9-30-57, New Orleans: Trip Passes, 1957 Annual Meeting"; July 9, 1957 to Sept. 26, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - "Annual, 9-30-57, New Orleans: 1957 Agenda"; July, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - "Annual, 9-30-57, New Orleans: 1957 Proceedings"; July 31, 1957 to Jan. 6, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - "1957 New Orleans Annual Meeting"; 1956-1957 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    Pictures
  - "1958 Annual Meeting, Savannah, Ga."; Oct. 1, 1956 to Oct. 14, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    Minutes, lists, correspondence
  - "1958 Annual Meeting, Savannah, Ga.: 1958 Agenda"; June 25, 1958 to Sept. 19, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    Correspondence, report, lists
  - "1958 Annual Meeting, Savannah, Ga.: Proceedings"; Apr. 18, 1958 to Dec. 12, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    Correspondence, speech, lists
    Correspondents: Thomas M. Healy, management member, U.S. Railroad Retirement Board
  - "1958 Annual Meeting, Savannah, Ga.: Annual Meeting, ASLRA, 1958"; July 1, 1958 to Sept. 22, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    Correspondence, pamphlets, speech
    Assoc. legislative policy (proposals), Transportation Act of 1958, legislation (railroad retirement and unemployment insurance)
    Correspondents: Everett Hutchinson, Commissioner, ICC
  - "Annual, 9-21-59, Washington"; Dec. 18, 1957 to Nov. 16, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    Correspondence, lists, speeches, minutes
    Correspondents: Daniel P. Loomis, Pres., Assoc. of American Railroads, Kenneth H. Tuggie, Chairman, Interstate Commerce Commission
  - "Annual Meeting, 9-21-59, Washington: Ladies Luncheon, Tour, etc."; Feb. 24, 1959 to Sept. 16, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    Correspondence, travel literature, menus, bills, memos
  - "Annual Meeting, 9-21-59, Washington: Trip passes, 1959"; July 21, 1959 to Sept. 17, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - "Annual Meeting, 1959, Agenda and Proceedings"; Dec. 5, 1958 to Aug. 8, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    Correspondence, reports, lists
  - Annual meeting, 1959, Washington; n.d. (Box 3, Folder 43)
    Brochures
  - "Annual, 10-3-60, Green Bay"; Aug. 1, 1958 to Nov. 17, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Lists, correspondence, speeches
  - "Annual, 10-3-60, Green Bay: Agenda and Proceedings, 1960"; July, 1960 to 10-19-60 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - "Annual, San Francisco, 1961: Special Board Meeting, Aug. 15, 1961"; Aug. 3, 1961 to Aug. 21, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - "Annual, San Francisco, 1961: 1961 Annual Meeting"; Sept. 16, 1957 to Feb. 2, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Correspondence, speeches, clippings, minutes, lists
    Correspondants: Leo E. Sievert, vice pres., Santa Fe Railroad, Thomas M. Healy, U.S. Railroad Retirement Board, Donald L. Manim, pres., ASLRA
  - "Annual, San Francisco, 1961: Agenda and Proceedings, 1961"; Sept. 7, 1961 to Feb. 2, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, lists, report, brochure
  - "1962 Annual Meeting" - Dallas; June 13, 1958 to Feb. 5, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Correspondence, lists, speeches, notes, memos, brochures
    Correspondents: Rupert L. Murphy, chairman, ICC, Thomas M. Healy, Railroad Retirement Board, Donald L. Manim, pres., ASLRA
  - "1962 Annual Meeting" - Dallas: "ASLRA - Agenda, 1962"; July 31, 1962 to Aug. 21, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - "1963 Annual Meeting" - Mississippi; July 6, 1961 to June 11, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Correspondence, lists, picture
  - "1963 Annual Meeting: Reporting - Annual Meeting"; Dec. 28, 1962 to Nov. 20, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - "1963 Annual Meeting: Agenda and Proceedings"; Oct. 9, 1962 to Apr. 3, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - "1964 Annual Meeting," Washington, D.C.; Nov. 24, 1961 to Jan. 21, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Correspondence, minutes, brochures, lists, memorabilia
  - "1964 Annual Meeting - Reporting"; Nov. 16, 1963 to Dec. 2, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - "1964 Annual Meeting - Agenda and Proceedings"; May 25, 1964 to Feb. 18, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - 1964 Annual Meeting - Arrangements - Ladies Committee; Feb. 6, 1964 to Oct. 2, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    Correspondence, memos
  - 1964 Annual Meeting - Misc; July 1, 1964 to Oct. 8, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Correspondence, speech, memos, memorabilia
  - Annual meeting, American Short Line Railroad Assoc; Oct. 3-4, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Minutes
  - Annual meeting, American Short Line Railroad Assoc; August 13-14-15, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Annual meeting, American Short Line Railroad Assoc; Dec. 8-9, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Annual meeting, American Short Line Railroad Assoc; Dec. 8-9, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - "Special Meeting, American Short Line Railroad Assoc."; Jan. 16-17, 1929 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Annual meeting, American Short Line Railroad Assoc; Dec. 5, 1929 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - "Eastern Regional Conference Meeting, American Short Line Railroad Assoc."; April 2, 1931 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Special meeting, American Short Line Railroad Assoc; Oct. 3-4, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Executive Board Meeting, American Short Line Railroad Assoc; May 20, 1933 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Annual meeting, American Short Line Railroad Assoc; June 23-24, 1933 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Annual meeting, American Short Line Railroad Assoc; Aug. 6-7, 1934 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Annual meeting, American Short Line Railroad Assoc; Oct. 21-22, 1935 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Annual meeting, American Short Line Railroad Assoc; Aug. 24-25, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Annual meeting, American Short Line Railroad Assoc; Oct. 18-19, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Annual meeting, American Short Line Railroad Assoc; Oct. 17-18, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Annual meeting, American Short Line Railroad Assoc; Oct. 23-24, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Annual meeting, American Short Line Railroad Assoc; Nov. 11-12, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Annual meeting, American Short Line Railroad Assoc; Sept. 29-30, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Annual meeting, American Short Line Railroad Assoc; Oct. 8-9, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Annual meeting, American Short Line Railroad Assoc; Oct. 2-3, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Annual Meeting, American Short Line Railroad Assoc; Oct. 21-22, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Annual Meeting, American Short Line Railroad Assoc; Oct. 13-14, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Annual Meeting, American Short Line Railroad Assoc; Sept. 27-28, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Annual Meeting, American Short Line Railroad Assoc; Oct. 3-4, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Annual Meeting, American Short Line Railroad Assoc; Oct. 3-4, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Annual Meeting, American Short Line Railroad Assoc; Oct. 2-3, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Annual Meeting, American Short Line Railroad Assoc; June 23, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Annual Meeting, American Short Line Railroad Assoc; Oct. 19-20, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Annual Meeting, American Short Line Railroad Assoc; Oct. 11, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Annual Meeting, American Short Line Railroad Assoc; Sept. 25-26, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Annual Meeting, American Short Line Railroad Assoc; Oct. 1-2, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Annual Meeting, American Short Line Railroad Assoc; Sept. 30 - Oct. 1, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Annual Meeting, American Short Line Railroad Assoc; Sept. 22-23, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Annual Meeting, American Short Line Railroad Assoc; Oct. 4-5, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Annual Meeting, American Short Line Railroad Assoc; Oct. 3-4, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Annual Meeting, American Short Line Railroad Assoc; Oct. 3-4, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Annual Meeting, American Short Line Railroad Assoc; Oct. 3-4, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Annual Meeting, American Short Line Railroad Assoc; Oct. 1-2, 1963, tr. 630
    Speeches, reports
    Correspondants: Paul B. Johnson, Lt. Governor of Mississippi, Lawrence K. Walrath, Chairman of the Interstate Commerce Commission; Paul Mathews, American Assoc. of Railroads; D. L. Manion, President of the American Short Line Railroad Assoc.
- Series II. Procedural Files, 1912-1967.
  General reference and technical records relating to such topics as classification, demurrage, freight rates, foreign tariffs, advertising, railroad financing, interline freight, government traffic and accident reports. Includes correspondence, handouts and reports from the Association of American Railroads on topics of interest to all member lines. There is an alphabetical file dealing with office procedures: tax forms and returns, bookkeeping files, Blue Cross and group hospitalization, a sampling of bills sent to member lines and membership cards used in billing. Statements, testimony and legislative material regarding the Hours of Service Act are included.
  - Agreements by the ICC re abandonments of railway properties; June 14, 1946 to Oct. 3, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - First Aid Instructions; Sept. 19, 1938 to May 28, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Correspondence, pamphlets
  - Miscellaneous Accident Investigations; Mar. 11, 1936 to June 19, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Handwritten votes, memos, reports, correspondence
  - Summary of Accidents Reported by All line Haul and S & T Railroad Crossings; June 63 to 11, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Statistical reports
  - Property Investment Account, Interstate Commerce Commission Docket #29803; Mar. 12, 1942 to Aug. 21, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Classification of Railroads; Aug. 12, 1935 to Apr. 1, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Closed out accounting releases; Feb. 16, 1955 to Jan. 9, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Questionnaires, correspondence, minutes, reports
  - Minimum Debt Rule Accounting; Feb. 5, 1947 to Jan. 27, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Railway Accounting Rules; Sept. 1, 1937 to Aug. 14, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    Report, correspondence
  - Proposed Revision of Accounting Regulation; Sept. 27, 1948 to Jan. 12, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Proposed Accounting Order; Jan. 22, 1942 to Jan. 31, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Correspondence, minutes, report
  - Interline Freight Settlements; Nov. 8, 1939 to May 28, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    Correspondence, memo, reports, minutes
  - Par Bank File; 18, 1949 to 10-20-59 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Directory of Freight Accounting Officers; Aug. 1, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    Correspondence, memo
  - Simplification of Passenger Tickets; May 16, 1944 to June 5, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    Correspondence, memos, circulars
  - Car Repair Vouchers and Bills; Aug. 14, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Pullman Tariffs; Oct. 4, 1950 to Apr. 20, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Overcharge Mandatory Rule 51; May 18, 1950 to Aug. 10, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Simplification of Joint Facility Bills and Vouchers; June 8, 1951 to July 31, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Scale and Pit Accounting; Sept. 53 to Dec. 23, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    Correspondence, article
  - Default on Freight Traffic Balances Due to Financial Distress; June 4, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Amortization Accounting; June 4, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    Order
  - Advertising; Oct. 15, 1938 to Nov. 10, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Joint Interregional Advertising Program - Sec. I; Nov. 14, 1945 to May 24, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Joint Interregional Advertising Program - Sec. II; May 18, 1948 to Feb. 5, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    Correspondence, article, examples of advertisements
  - Joint Interregional Advertising Program Charges for participation; Sept. 17, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    List, bill
  - Joint Interregional Advertising Program Examples of advertisements; 1947 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    Correspondence, broadsides
  - Joint Interregional Advertising Program "Study of Readership.."; March 1947 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Joint Interregional Advertising Program Advertisement Reaction; June 1947 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Joint Interregional Advertising Program "The Railroad Dollar"; n.d. (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Joint Interregional Advertising Program "Liberty and Taxes"; n.d. (Box 7, Folder 31)
    Manuscript
  - Revision of Annual Report; June 18, 1954 to Jan. 15, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - AAR - Car Service Division; Jan. 26, 1956 to June 26, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Correspondence, service orders
  - AAR - Mechanical Division; Jan. 8, 1957 to Dec. 26, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Transportation Charges - Sec. I; Apr. 22, 1921 to Oct. 26, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Reports, ICC orders, correspondence
  - Correspondence with CSS and SB on Awards - Third Division, NRAB; July 30, 1938 to Apr. 5, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Ex Parte 175, Increased Freight Rates, Sec. I; Nov. 3, 1950 to Dec. 7, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Increased Freight rates (Ex Parte), Sec. II; Dec. 13, 1951 to Mar. 31, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Orders, petitions, correspondence
  - Railway Express; Mar. 2, 1950 to Aug. 4, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Correspondence, directives, reports, statistical data
  - Railway Express Agency Expenses; May 21, 1948 to Sept. 24, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, ICC rulings, reports, statistical data
  - Disaster Loan Applications; Sept. 12, 1955 to Sept. 23, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Memos, instructions, application
  - Fluctuations in Railroad Freight Traffic, etc; Sept. 7, 1960 to Feb. 4, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Correspondence, directives, memos
  - Cost of Living Index - Special Section; Dec. 1, 1950 to Sept. 24, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Correspondence, circulars, memos
  - Sioux City Terminal Switching Case; July 8, 1940 to May 22, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Correspondence, memos, notes, orders
  - Freight Traffic Improvement Progress Report; 1912, 1936, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    Reports
  - Jones Combination Rule Etc; Oct. 26, 1923 to Jan. 12, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Legality of Tariffs, Motor Trucks or Wagon, etc; Apr. 9, 1923 to July 16, 1924 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Mileage Tariff No. 7; Jan. 28, 1935 to Jan. 11, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    Correspondence, orders, lists
  - Expense of Printing Freight Tariffs; July 27, 1938 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    Directive
  - Distribution of Freight Tariff Improvement Bulletins; Nov. 3, 1938 to June 5, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Shippers Service Bureau; Jan. 27, 1939 to Jan. 1, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    Advertisments, correspondence
  - Movement of Petroleum Under Tariff of Reduced Rates; Nov. 8, 1941 to Dec. 19, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Petition of Celotex Corp. for Suspension of Tariffs; Mar. 26, 1941 to Apr. 10, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Interpretation of Freight Tariffs; Feb. 17, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Expense for Distributing Tariffs; Aug. 3, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    Letter
  - Freight Tariff Improvement Progress Report; July 21, 1952 to May 22, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Ex Parte 199 Office Hours for Filing Freight and Passenger; Feb. 6, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    Notice
  - Internal Revenue Code of 1954; Dec. 4, 1941 to Mar. 27, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Victory Tax; Nov. 30, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Transport of Alcholic Liquors to Officers' Clubs, Px, etc; June 27, 1941 to July 27, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Mobile and Ohio Railroad vs. State Tax Commission; Aug. 7, 1940 to Aug. 15, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Undistributed Profits Tax; Jan. 26, 1937 to Feb. 15, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    Correspondence, clippings, questionnairs, calendar
  - Undistributed Profits tax; 1938 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    Speech
  - Ad Valorem Taxes - State of California; Oct. 17, 1929 to Oct. 22, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Railroad Franchise Tax in North Carolina; Aug. 30, 1938 to Feb. 21, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    Correspondence, reports, pamphlet
  - District of Columbia vs. Southern Railway Tax Case; May 15, 1950 to Mar. 9, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    Correspondence, court petition, articles, report
  - Tax Matters; Sept. 25, 1948 to June 26, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Digest of State Laws, Motor Vehicles; Jan. 5, 1949 to Jan. 24, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Vacation Pay Accruals; May 21, 1948 to May 1, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    Correspondence, memos, directives
  - Internal Revenue Act of 1948; 1948 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    Government document, pamphlets
  - Ceiling on Federal Taxation; Oct. 25, 1944 to Nov. 13, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    Correspondence, pamphlet
  - Withholding Tax; May 20, 1943 to Mar. 4, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    Correspondence, forms, directives, reports
  - Regulation 42 - Taxes on Safe Deposit Boxes, etc; Apr. 3, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    Government document
  - Detroit, Cairo and Sandusky Railway Co; Apr. 26, 1941 to Mar. 3, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    Correspondence, statistical data
  - Property Transportation Tax; Apr. 11, 1950 to June 19, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Refund of Taxes on Overcharge Claims; July 6, 1950 to Apr. 6, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Tax Amendments etc; 1937, 1954-1955 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    Letters, government document
  - Tax Bill, Public Law 814; Sept. 26, 1950 to Oct. 16, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    Correspondence, legislative bill, pamphlets
  - Employee Tax Regulations; July 29, 1954 to June 14, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    Reports, pamphlets, correspondence
  - Passenger Car Tickets; Sept. 22, 1949 to June 5, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Tie Plates; May 6, 1946 to Feb. 9, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Correspondence, advertisements
  - Cross Ties; Aug. 5, 1952 to Mar. 19, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Cross ties - replies to Class III and Electric Lines; Sept. 3, 1952 to Oct. 17, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    Correspondence, lists, questionnaire
  - Cross Ties; Apr. 25, 1952 to Nov. 26, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, speech
  - Committee 03 on Cross Ties and Switch Ties; Jan. 13, 1953 to Apr. 2, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Track Removal; June 17, 1939 to Mar. 12, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Lawndale Railway & Industrial Co. Change from Narrow to Standard Gauge; Sept. 23, 1943 to Sept. 25, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Track Scales - For sale and wanted; July 7, 1945 to Oct. 29, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    Advertisements, correspondence
  - Interline tickets - Form of Records; Oct. 10, 1931 to Apr. 21, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Transportation Act - Policy; Oct. 19, 1944 to Aug. 5, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    Correspondence, legislative bill
  - Florida Barge Canal; Sept. 3, 1935 to Oct. 14, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    Legislative bill, correspondence, reports, news articles
  - Canal vs. Railroad transportation; Oct. 7, 1935 to Oct. 26, 1935 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    Correspondence, broadside
  - Trinity River Project; Oct. 25, 1937 to Oct. 20, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    Correspondence, articles, hearing, testimony
  - Savannah River Barge Line; May 13, 1937 to Aug. 7, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Tolls on New York Barge and other canals; Feb. 20, 1940 to Mar. 11, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    Correspondence, memos, lists
  - Federal Aid to waterways; 1940 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - U.S. Public Health Reports; 1921, 1924-1926 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    Correspondents: United State Public Health Service
  - Missouri Basin Survey Commission; Jan. 3, 1952 to Jan. 4, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Weights and Measures; 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    Magazine, pamphlet, weight and measure
  - Wharfingers Ex Parte 144; May 5, 1941 to Feb. 19, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    Correspondence, briefs
  - Foreign-owned Equipment; Nov. 1, 1934 to Aug. 22, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    Correspondence, memos, report
  - Equipment for Sale; July 1, 1945 to May 1, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Surplus Property, Section I; May 12, 1944 to Dec. 28, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    Correspondence, press releases, lists
  - Surplus Property, Section II; Dec. 31, 1945 to Dec. 16, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    Correspondence, press releases, lists reports
  - Surplus Property, Section III; Jan. 13, 1947 to Dec. 15, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    Correspondence, notices, lists
  - Surplus Property; 1944-1946, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    Pamphlets, reports
  - Communications Data; 1950, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Advertising booklet, correspondence
  - Navigational Clearance Requirements; 1955 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    Report, multicopy diagram
  - Railway Bridge Spans for Sale; July 30, 1945 to Jan. 26, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Correspondence, notices
  - Overruled Dicisions of Supreme Court; Aug. 15, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Decisions of U.S. Court of Claims; Feb. 6, 1951 to Mar. 12, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Potters Supreme Court Service; May 8, 1952 to Apr. 20, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    Correspondence, lists, newsletter
  - Competitive Transportation; June 21, 1949 to 8, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    Newsletters, reports, correspondence, bulletins
  - Selective Service; July 28, 1948 to July 16, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    Memo, reports, correspondence
  - Selective Service; Aug. 11, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Selective Service - Misc. copies of Selective Service material; 1945 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Government document, forms
  - Abraham Fishgold vs. Sullivan Dry Dock et. al.; May 27, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Bush Terminal Pick-up and Delivery - FD 14137; May 29, 1941 to Dec. 12, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    Correspondence, reports, charts
  - Bush Terminal Pick-up and Delivery; May 31, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    Acquisition of facilities petition to intervene
    Correspondents: Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freighthandlers, Express and Station employees
  - Bush Terminal Pick-up and Delivery; 1943-1944 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    Legal briefs, lease
  - Federal Jurisdiction over Interstate Commerce; Apr. 15, 1921 to Aug. 6, 1940 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    Correspondence, memos, reports
  - Financing of Interstate Roads; Oct. 21, 1936 to Apr. 20, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    Senate Resolution, correspondence, memos, news articles
  - Financing of Interstate Roads; 1939-1941 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Financing of Interstate Roads; 1939-1940 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    Press releases
  - Mortgage Bonds; Mar. 25, 1938 to Mar. 17, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    Correspondence, news articles
  - Government Traffic; Sept. 6, 1950 to May 7, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Lendlease; Nov. 30, 1943 to Apr. 23, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Lendlease; 1941-1943 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Export Traffic; Oct. 31, 1941 to Dec. 5, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Work Rules Dispute Miscellaneous Papers; Feb. 1, 1963 to Apr. 11, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Correspondence, reports, memos, press releases, statements
  - Hours of Service Act; 1965-1967 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Legislative bill, memos, lists, statement